John B-PER
lives O
in O
New B-LOC
York I-LOC
. O

This O
is O
another O
sentence

Peter B-PER
Blackburn I-PER
